cooking-games.biz 2011-03-14

# Privacy Policy

**Introduction**   
We are committed to providing a fun, entertaining, and safe Web site for people of all ages. We are dedicated to safeguarding any personal information collected online and to helping parents and children learn how to exercise control over personal information while exploring the Internet. Because many of the visitors to this site are children, we take special measures to help children protect their privacy while online. For example, we do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity, and we take efforts to prevent children from posting contact information. This Privacy Policy is intended to explain our privacy practices and inform you as to:   

  * 1\. The kinds of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") we collect from visitors.
  * 2\. How that information is collected. 
  * 3\. How we use Personal Information. 
  * 4\. The circumstances under which we disclose Personal Information to third parties. 
  * 5\. How you can access, update or delete any Personal Information collected about you by us.
  * 6\. The mechanisms we have implemented to protect your Personal Information.

As we continue to offer our visitors new and different types of content and services, we may modify our practices from time to time. However, we will treat all personal information we collect in accordance with the privacy notice in effect at the time the information is collected. This Privacy Policy is a part of the terms and conditions which are set forth in our Terms of Use Agreement ("Agreement"). Any terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning given in the Agreement. 

**The Information We Collect**   
We only collect personal information from registered members. Visitors are required to be 13 years or older to register. During the registration we collect a username (login), valid e-mail address, password and birth date, we may collect additional information including Computer Information (see below), and we may ask additional questions regarding personal preferences on a number of topics through surveys. For certain enhanced services, we also may collect billing information provided by PayPal. Additionally, when visitors come to our site, we automatically collect some non-personally identifiable "computer" information, such as the type of computer operating system (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), the visitor's "IP Address", the web browser (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer) being used, information collected through the use of cookies (see below) and information regarding the Internet service provider ("Computer Information"). This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

**How We Use the Information**   
User Profile information including members', pictures and sign-in names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the social networking community. Email addresses are used to send notifications related to the service. 

We use visitors' Personal Information for our internal purposes of enabling visitors to enter one of our online contests or sweepstakes, to subscribe to our online newsletter, or to inform visitors of upcoming events and special announcements. Each e-mail contains instructions on how to be removed from the subscription list. 

We also use visitors' Computer Information to track usage, improve the design of the Site, offer products and services, to personalize our visitor's experiences, save your password in password-protected areas, and to ensure visitors are following the site's Agreement. 

We may disclose information about our visitors, including Personal Information (e.g., registration information, e-mail address), as well as Computer Information, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Site and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site. We also may disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of our visitors or others. 

**Cookies**   
We use a software technology called "cookies." Cookies are small text files that we and certain third parties place in visitors' computer browsers to store their preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. 

We may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy. 

You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other Web site. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. However, certain areas of our sites can only be accessed in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content. 

**Security**   
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

Phishing: Phishing attacks attempt to steal consumers' personal identity data and financial account credentials. "Phishers" use 'spoofed' e-mails to lead consumers to counterfeit websites designed to trick recipients into divulging Sensitive Personal Information such as credit card numbers, account usernames, passwords, and social security numbers. WE DO NOT SEND EMAILS ASKING YOU TO PROVIDE OR CONFIRM SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION OR YOUR USERNAME OR PASSWORD! If you receive such email communication, please forward it immediately to the Site's Privacy Administrator at privacy@manydressupgames.com and then immediately delete the fraudulent email from your computer. 

**Additional Information Concerning Children's Privacy**   
We do not collect Personal Information from visitors who identify themselves as under the age of 13. Visitors to our site may participate in many of our offerings and activities without providing any Personal Information. As noted above, we will not condition participation in an online activity on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. We do not share children's Personal Information with outside third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy. 

Our goal is to help parents ensure that their kids have a safe and fun online experience. That's why we've set up a system by which parents can contact us to review any Personal Information collected about their child, have this information corrected or deleted, and/or request that there be no further collection or use of their child's information. Please make any such request through this e-mail address: privacy@manydressupgames.com. We take steps to verify the identity of anyone requesting information about a child and to ensure that the person is in fact the child's parent or legal guardian. 

**Third Parties**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

**Accessing or Correcting Information**   
Visitors can change their user information supplied upon registration (except for email and login) on this page: Edit Profile and following the direction on such page. 

**Contact Us**   
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our privacy policy and/or practices, please contact us at:   
privacy@manydressupgames.com 

**Effective Date, Updates and Acceptance**   
The privacy policy set out above is effective as of February 15, 2008. Your use of the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use Agreement. By using this Site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Your continued use of any portion of the Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.
